Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun had launched an assault on the Forest of Witches, hoping to get their hands on the magic stone that was said to be found there.
Meanwhile, the forest was also beset by the Diamond Kingdom, who had come to take advantage of the confusion and learn the secret of a magic technique that prevented the Queen of Witches from growing old.
Fonzel, who was once an officer in that same army, was forced to fight Mars and Ladros, two of his former students.
MILLION LASERS!
Ladros, stop. Please, I beg you. Use your power for what's right.
There's nothing better than getting an opportunity to use your power to the absolute max, and devastating any opponent that dares to stand in your way!
My goal is to be recognized all over this nation, and eventually the whole world!
I think I'll start by killing this noisy little witch!
Domino!
My powers are for protecting people.
Everything that you said, well, I guess it finally hit home.
But Mars had a change of heart.
He decided to help the weak and Fonzel contend with Ladros' unique magic ability, which was absorbing magic power and releasing it at will.
Hey! Are you guys talking about me?
Doesn't matter how great your plan is, it'll be useless against my magic!
I've got a knack for reinforcement spells myself!
So say goodbye!
Let's go!
Bye!
See you next time.
Bounce it over here!
Don't see why, but sure!
A wind will send us flying so the flame gets through.
That's more power than I can hold.
Everyone okay?
See you next time.
Looks like our strategy worked.
Hey!
What is your deal?
I still don't understand!
What fell from this guy?
That was amazing, Asta.
You've really gotten stronger.
Yeah, it was nothing, really.
But go on.
Wait, forget about that!
I wanna know why you're hanging out with Frosty here!
He's a bad guy!
Asta, isn't it?
You and I are not enemies.
Trust me.
How can I trust a scary-looking face like that?
By the way, the name's Mars, Pipsqueak.
Now you're just being rude!
I'll explain things later.
But for now, I need you to listen to him.
Well, if you say so, I guess I can.
Good to hear.
Now then.
Thanks to you, we don't have to worry about Ladras anymore, but...
Our next problem is this thing.
So that's the Fire Spirit Salamander I've heard about.
Despite being weakened.
It's magic is extraordinary.
But...
Those flames...
They're the same as mine.
And it's power feels identical, too.
It's...
Volana.
There's no one to save us. We have no choice, but...
Mars, is our training getting to you?
No, I'm fine.
When things get tough, just close your eyes and think about the people you love.
That's why we're here.
We were born so we could become powerful enough to protect our country.
People I love.
The first face I thought of was yours.
Fauna.
Once we've gotten strong, that's when we'll get to leave this place.
Do you think you'll be the first one who goes?
I do.
I mean...
How could you not be?
You're the strongest.
We all know it.
What?
If I get out, I'll wait.
I promise.
I'll wait for you.
Yeah.
We'll go see the outside world together.
This is your final test.
A fight to the death.
Only the last one standing will be permitted to leave here as a mage in service to our country.
Refuse, and you will all be eliminated.
Mars, I'm sorry.
Fauna?
This is the only way.
Now die.
The two are only necessities of course figures and death must imme幾乎 ~!
You mile in number foureroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroeroero now and meanwhile Blockцаo are lasing at 644 ~!
7276 002 runway 18673 002 jobs UAk
So you Hillary, Sinne thank you Harry, chronicへ。
His
Why did you...
Why, Fauna?
What?
I had to do it, Mars.
I'm sorry.
Now go see the outside world.
You've earned it.
Live your life, Mars.
For both of us.
Fauna!
I killed her with my own hands.
I know it.
And yet, she's alive somehow.
Fauna!
It's me, remember?
Please, tell me you still recognize me!
Wait a second!
If you get any closer, she's gonna burn you to a crisp!
What's gotten into you?
I'm your friend!
Come on!
Talk to me!
Fauna!
I know that girl.
I taught her.
I heard she died a while back during one of Morse's human experiments.
Fauna!
Get away from me!
I don't know who you are!
Oh!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
That is her, no doubt.
But wait.
Is she casting a transformation spell?
No, there'd be nothing to gain from that.
The spell is emanating from that strange eye.
Someone else must be casting it.
The eye of the Midnight Sun have been controlling her!
What.. is this?
My head hurts!
What's wrong?!
The eye of the Midnight Sun, they must be controlling her!
What.. is this?!
My head hurts?!
What's wrong?!
You're all in my way. You always are.
I hate you!
What's that?
Crap! More self-destructing?
I'm taking you with me, all of you!
In fact, I'm going to blow this entire temple away!
Oh no.
Why do all these Midnight Sun people think that's the solution to everything?
If we don't do something quickly, then this entire area will be blown sky high.
Everything must be destroyed.
Seat Dragon Slayer!
Mars, get out of there!
Are you seriously just going to let her kill you?
Use your magic to block!
No, Master.
I have no right to live.
I killed Fauna.
And so, I should die.
There's no time for dumb stuff like that!
Do you want to die?
I don't understand all the details, but are you positive that girl is your friend?
She's working with the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
She's got three eyes.
Maybe you're confused.
I'd never mistake anyone for her.
She's my dear friend.
Always has been.
She's dear to you?
Okay.
If that's the case, then that means you have even more reason not to die!
Just live!
Then you can save her for good!
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Well, that didn't take much.
Forget seniority.
Asta's got no problem chewing anybody out.
Don't worry, Mars.
You've grown into someone strong enough to save Fauna for sure.
With my thread magic and Finral's spatial magic, we are still useless against her power.
And a jolt from Noelle's water magic might set off the explosion.
The only way we can stop her is with Asta's anti-magic sword.
All right, you big lizard!
Come on and get some!
Asta!
When I fought that hairy guy...
Don't waste your time!
You humans will taste despair!
Despair!
My strength alone wasn't enough.
When we were kids, I killed my best friend.
But this time, we won't fail!
I'm warning you!
Stay back!
Mineral magic!
Laser time!
They're both outstanding.
Facing that flame magic at close range like it's nothing.
But they've only got so much time left.
Can they make it?
If I swing my sword far enough, I can counter her self-destruct magic!
Man, it's hot!
If I get any closer, I'll be toast!
Oh, no!
Wait!
He's fine!
Did you...
I used Phoenix's robe.
It heals you.
See?
You ready?
Yeah!
As long as I'm not getting turned into barbecue, I'm good to go!
This boy is unbelievable.
I fought with my share of people after doing battle with him in the dungeon.
Get on!
I can do this!
But no one I met was this dead set of not giving up.
And he's so strange.
Not exactly his foe or his ally.
Yet he chose to encourage and help me.
And of all the Clover Kingdom Magic Knights I've met before,
none of them have gone this far to protect and save another person.
Everything they claim to stand for,
he genuinely embodies it.
He's a true knight.
You doing okay over there?
Of course.
This is painful,
but it's nothing compared to Fauna's suffering.
This guy's really changed a lot since the first time I fought him.
At first he was like some evil doll,
but now he seems to have a heart.
If he's that strong and that determined to help someone he cares about,
nothing in the whole world can stop him.
Any minute she'll explode.
Hey, you three, run for cover!
They're staying?
They must have a lot of faith in their friend.
Then I'm going to have faith too.
In my students.
I know you can do this, Mars and Asta.
Everyone's counting on you.
Almost there.
Fauna!
It's all over!
No it isn't!
Not yet!
We won't let it be!
Wow, it worked!
Ah crap, this is really hot!
It's over!
No it's not!
Our hatred can't be stamped out, ever!
No way!
Fauna!
It's me, remember?
I'm so sorry!
I didn't have the strength to fight beside you back then!
But please, forgive me!
You're a girl, Fauna.
It's not a good idea to overdo it.
If I get out, I'll wait.
I promise I will.
I'm sorry!
That's it!
Not a good idea today.
What?!
Close the door!
Run!
Everybody on this day!
He did this!
He's the only one that knows this place!
I knew it!
That human betrayed all of us!
He did this!
He's the only one that knows this place!
Let's keep our promise, okay?
Someday, we'll see the world.
Let us explore together!
We said we would, so let's go.
Right, Pana.
What's wrong?
Well, that's a relief.
Yeah, I'm glad.
Lucky!
We'll see you next time.
Bye.
Boateng.
CLOVER CLIPS
Leave it to Mars.
By the way, Mars.
How's your life been going since you defeated me?
I still feel really bad about that.
Ta-da!
Look at this grimoire.
That's odd.
Looks half like mine.
Right!
That's because it's been imbued with your magic power.
That way, you're always with me.
Wow, that's creepy.
Well, it was made by Morris, the Mage Scholar.
He wiped my memories and modified my body.
So I was forced to fight who I was told.
But battling Asta in that dungeon made me remember.
And here's the best part.
In an effort to make it up to you,
I always found a way to secretly help people during my missions.
Nice, right?
Yes, good boy.
You still hurt me, but good boy.
I'm so jealous, I can't stand it!
But since I'm his elder, I'll take the high road on this one.
I am older than him, right?
Anyway, congrats to Mars and Fauna, I guess.
Black Clover, page 62.
Bettering one another.
Nope, still jealous!
Yes!
Okay.